Arnold Emil Frontend Developer

■ genuine5621@gmail.com
○ Chorzowska 8 Krakow, Poland

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/arnold-emil-5594a42a9/

PROFILE

I'm an experienced front-end developer with a solid background in everything related to online marketing on top. It is my passion to build sleek & well-optimized websites and web apps. I'm very much into gaming and learning to work with new technologies, always improving myself to stay on top of my field. Further, I like nature and enjoy doing some trekking from time to time. Finally, I'm a good person to have a beer with.

EDUCATION

Oct 2012 – Jul 2016 Cracow, Poland **Cracow University of Technology** *Bachelor's degree of Computer Science*

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Feb 2021 – present Krakow, Poland

TRIMSY

Frontend Developer

- Increased daily traffic from 45% to 80% in E-commerce platforms by redesigning existing websites to improve user experience and incorporated SEO
- Designed and developed interfaces that simplify dense information streams and solicit user interactions with machine learning feedback systems that feel intuitive and familiar
- Collaborated on Complexity Score tool, which removed process bottlenecks by assigning scores to cost, time, and compliance issues, increasing efficiency by 72%
- Developed app integration with REST and other APIs for Google Maps, social media logins, payment processors, and other services
- Collaborated with 2 different development teams on 4 new project designs and feature improvements
- Suggested 20+ improvements to product design and functionality as informed by user-experience reporting
- Collaborated with 4 client service teams to understand and solve bottlenecks and proposed feature expansions

Jul 2017 – Feb 2021 Tehran, Iran

Parvan Pajooh

Frontend Developer

- Worked with advanced web development technologies like React, Typescript, JavaScript, Bootstrap 4, CSS, SASS, and HTML.
- Worked with several React UI libraries like Ant design and Material UI.
- Created compatible customer client dashboards.
- Worked with UX/UI design teams to improve existing applications.

- used Jira tool for requirement gathering, GitHub, and Git Lab as version control systems.
- used multiple state management like Redux, Context, Recoil

Jul 2016 – May 2017 Krakow, Poland

NEEDCODE

Office Manager

Main areas of application:

Technical infrastructure and website maintenance,

office administration and organization,

Seminar operation

Seminar organization:

Preparation of advertising measures

(advertisements, banner advertising, print templates), social media support,

Newsletter creation and sending

GDPR:

Significant participation in the creation a data protection declaration, processing of order processing contracts

Accounting:

Accounting preparation for the

Tax advice

SKILLS

- Responsive Web Design
- JavaScript & TypeScript
- React.js

Angular.js

Vue.js

• Svelte

- PHP & Laravel
- WordPress & Shopify
- Node.js & Express

• MySQL

• MongoDB

S LANGUAGES

Polish English C2 B2